<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OpenDataApp</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="sports_list">Sports list</string>
    <string name="information_menu_icon">Information</string>

    <string name="app_name_info">Sport Places Finder</string>
    <string name="app_description">This Android application uses a database that lists all the sports locations in the world. It thus allows the user to know where to go to practice the sport he has selected.\n\nIn order to retrieve the data, the client sends a GET request to the server, in the following form: https://sportplaces.api.decathlon.com/api/v1/places?origin=x&amp;radius=y&amp;sports=z with x: the user\'s current position. y: the search radius in km. z: the code identifying the indicated sport. Each sport is associated with a unique code.\n\nData URL: https://sportplaces.api.decathlon.com/api/v1/places</string>
    <string name="author">Authors</string>
    <string name="author_chevalier">Jean-Christophe Chevalier</string>
    <string name="author_ladriere">Alexandre Ladrière</string>
    <string name="linkedin_chevalier"><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jean-christophe-chevalier/">linkedin.com/in/jean-christophe-chevalier</a></string>
    <string name="linkedin_ladriere"><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexandre-ladriere/">linkedin.com/in/alexandre-ladriere</a></string>
    <string name="github_chevalier"><a href="https://github.com/jcchevalier">github.com/jcchevalier</a></string>
    <string name="github_ladriere"><a href="https://github.com/AlexandreLadriere">github.com/AlexandreLadriere</a></string>
    <string name="context">Context</string>
    <string name="context_content">This Android application is the result of a project, carried out as part of an Android development course as part of our training at the Ecole Nationale des Mines de Saint-Etienne.\n\nLink to the GitHub repository: <a href="https://github.com/ISMIN-Design-Of-Mobile-Application/open-data-android-app-AlexandreLadriere">https://github.com/ISMIN-Design-Of-Mobile-Application/open-data-android-app-AlexandreLadriere</a></string>
    <string name="licence">Licence</string>
    <string name="licence_content"><![CDATA[ MIT License\n\nCopyright © 2019 Alexandre Ladrière & Jean-Christophe Chevalier\n\nPermission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:\n\nThe above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.\n\nTHE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.]]></string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connexion">No Internet Connexion</string>
    <string name="offline_message">You are offline. Please check your internet connection if you want to use all features of this app</string>
    <string name="close">CLOSE</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="google_maps_key">AIzaSyDTvIgeeBFG2uXzuraR7TVbDs4TSZL_IGg</string>
    <string name="gps_off">GPS Offline</string>
    <string name="gps_off_message">This application need to use your GPS. Please turn on your GPS.</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="results_count">0 results</string>
    <string name="search_in_this_area">\u0020\u0020 Search in this area \u0020\u0020</string>
    <string name="results">results</string>
</resources>
